hold pan
move pan
open cupboard
pickup herb
open herb
sprinkle herb on meat
close herb
put herb
open drawer
get spoon
open fridge
pickup yogurt
put yogurt
put spoon
pick up the honey
open the honey
pick up spoon
mix the honey
stirring tahini
scoop tahini
put tahini on meat
pour tahini on meat
close tahini
put tahini away
open yogurt
pickup spoon
scoop yogurt
put yogurt
put spoon
close yogurt
mix meat
stir meat with yogurt and tahini
open drawer
get topperware
get spoon
close drawer
open topperware
pick up meat
put meat in topperware
put in topperware
pick up meat
put spoon
close topperware
put topperware away
hold pan
stir meat with tahini and yogurt
mixing meat
open yogurt
pick up spoon
scoop yogurt
pour yogurt
put spoon
put yogurt
hold pan
stir meat with yogurt
still stirring meat
taste meat mix
stir meat
pick up pan
put pan
Move pan
Open cupboard
Pick up tray
Move bags
Close cupboard
Pick up tray
Put tray
Open cupboard
Return tray
Pick up another tray
Remove lid
Put lid
Close cupboard
Shake tray
move tray
put tray
pickup plate
move can
get thyme
put plate
put thyme
set off timer
open oven
pull drawer
pickup bowl
push drawer
close oven
move tray
set off timer
put bowl
remove towels
close drawer
open drawer
put towels
close drawer
kneed dough
kneed dough in bowl
hold bowl
kneed dough
move bowl
pickup tray
put tray
move paper towel
move pan
move tray
pickup olive oil
open olive oil bottle
Pickup olive oil
Pour oil onto tray
Put olive oil bottle
Spread olive in tray
Pickup dough
Get a bowl of dough
Pickup olive oil
Pour olive oil in plate
Put olive oil
Pickup some oil
Knead dough in hand
Roll dough.
Put bowl of dough.
get bowl of dough.
Pickup oil.
Knead dough.
Roll dough.
Pickup oil
spread oil on hand.
Get a bowl of dough.
knead bowl of dough.
roll bowl of dough.
Put bowl of dough.
get some oil
spread oil on hand
get ball of dough
knead ball of dough
roll ball of dough
put ball of dough
get some oil
spread oil on hand
get ball of dough
knead ball of dough
roll ball of dough
get some oil
put ball of dough
Get bowl of dough
Get some oil
Knead bowl of dough
Roll bowl of dough
Get some oil
Put bowl of dough
Spread oil on hand
Get bowl of dough
Knead bowl of dough
Get some oil
Pick up oil bottle
Pour oil bottle into plate
Put bottle of oil
Get some oil
Spread oil on hand
knead ball of dough
roll ball of dough
put ball of dough
get some oil
spread oil on hand
get ball of dough
knead ball of dough
roll ball of dough
put ball of dough
get some meat from pan
put meat on raw ball of dough
get some meat
put meat on bowl of dough
squeeze
get some meat, put meat on bowl of dough
get meat put meat on bowl of dough
get meat mix put meat on bowl of dough
get meat mix put mix on bowl of dough
get meat mix
put mix on ball of dough
get meat mix from pan
put mix meat on ball of dough
put meat mix on ball of dough
get meat mix from pan
PICK UP TRAY
PUT TRAY ON STOVE
PUT TRAY
PICK UP PLATE
POUR OIL FROM PLATE TO TRAY
SPREAD OIL IN TRAY
PICK UP PLATE POUR OIL IN TRAY
GET BALL OF DOUGH FROM BOWL
KNEAD DOUGH
ROLL BALL OF DOUGH
Put bowl of dough
Turn oven on
Get bowl of dough
Knead bowl of dough
Roll bowl of dough
Put bowl of dough
Get bowl of dough
Get some oil
Knead bowl of dough
Roll bowl of dough
Put bowl of dough
Get some oil
Spread oil on hand
Get bowl of dough
Knead bowl of dough
roll ball of dough
put ball of dough
get some oil
spread oil on hand
get ball of dough
kneed ball of dough
get some oil
roll ball of dough
put ball of dough
get some oil
spread oil on hand
get ball of dough
get some oil
spread oil on hand
kneed ball of dough
roll
put ball of dough
get meat mix
put meat mix on dough
get meat mix from pan
get mix meat from pan
put meat mix on dough
get meat mix from pan
get meat mix from pan from spoon
put meat mix on dough
get meat mix from pan
open cupboard
get tray
remove bags
pickup tray
put tray
pickup plate
pour oil
-Pick up olive oil bottle
-Pour oil on tray
-Spread oil in tray
-Pick up dough, half dough
-Knead ball of dough
-Roll Knead ball of dough
-Roll ball of dough
-Put ball of dough
-Pick up ball of dough
-Knead ball of dough
-Roll ball of dough
-Put ball of dough on tray
-Open drawer
-Pick up spoon
Pick up olive oil bottle
Pour olive oil in plate
Put olive oil bottle
Open jar
Scoop thyme
Put thyme in plate
Mix thyme and olive oil in plate
Scoop thyme and olive oil using hand
Put thyme and olive oil on dough
Put plate
Pick up tray
pickup olive oil bottle
pour olive oil into plate
return bottle
hold plate
get thyme
mix thyme in plate
pickup olive oil
add olive
mix olive oil and thyme
pickup plate
hold plate
scoop olive oil and thyme
put olive oil and thyme into dough
put mixture of olive oil and thyme onto dough
sccop olive oil and dough from plate
add olive oil and thyme to dough
pour olive oil and thyme from plate to dough
put plate
scoop thyme using spoon
add thyme to dough
pour thyme from plate to dough
put plate in sink
open tap
wash hands
pick up towel
dry hands
open cupboard
pick up pine nuts
pour pine nuts into hand
place pine nuts
add pine nuts to pie
pick up pine nuts from hand
put pine nuts on pie
pick up pine nuts bag
pour pine nuts bag into hand
put pine nuts bag
add pine nuts to pie
pick up pine nuts bag
pour pine nuts into hand
return pine nuts bags
add pine nuts unto pie
add pine nuts to pie
put pine nuts on pie
pick up pine nuts bag
open fridge
return bag
close fridge
pick up towel
pick up oven gloves
open oven
remove oven tray
push oven tray
close oven
remove oven glove
[END SUBTITLE]